让我们一起执行一个更为复杂的 Node.js 应用程序，
Let's together do a more
Complicated Node.js Application so,
我们就是喜欢 " Hello World " 或 " 我的上帝" ( lol of Node.js ) ，对吧 ?
we just did like the Hello World or
the my God, lol of Node.js, right?
就是说不是很现实的应用是一个
Which is to say is not a very
realistic application it's one
被执行的文件，以及我们如何进入更复杂的措施
file that's executed and, kind of where
we get into more complicated measures
对于 " 节点 " 应用程序，我们必须开始担心 " 依赖性 " ，对吗 ?
with Node applications is we have to
start worrying about Dependencies, right?
这实际上是我们在混合中 Docker 的一半原因
This is actually kind of like half the
reason we have Docker in the mix at all is
我们可以冻结和控制我们的依赖性
that we can freeze and
control our dependencies, right?
就像大多数人知道的，节点有这个叫做 MPM 的东西， MPM 不代表
So as most people know, node has this
thing called MPM, MPM does not stand for
节点软件包管理器，但它是节点软件包管理器。
node package manager, but
it is the node package manager.
所以我们要做的就是把这个文件留在这里
So we're going to do is I have this file
here inside of the more complicated no JS
我们要做的就是重新开始我们的项目
app, what we're gonna do is we're gonna
go over to our project again, and
我要打开我的侧边栏我要说新文件夹
I'm gonna open my sidebar here,
and I'm gonna say New Folder.
这个会被称为更复杂的 nodejs-app，好吗 ?
And this one's gonna be called
more-complicated-nodejs-app, okay?
在这里我要再创造一个新的文件
Inside of here,
I'm gonna create a new file, this again,
将被称为 index.js ，我将会复制这里的所有内容。
will be called index.js, and I'm going
to be copying everything that's in here.
你可以在这里看到我越来越多的人
Which you can see here I more or
less took from the hapi-pino example,
hapi.js 是最受欢迎的 Node.js 服务器端框架之一，
hapi.js is one of the most popular
Node.js server-side frameworks,
就像 Express，我挺喜欢的，我的好友艾兰 - 哈默写的。
it's like Express, I quite like it,
my good friend Eran Hammer writes it.
这也做了同样的事情，它有一些记录功能，
And this does relatively the same thing,
it has some logging functionality,
这才是暂时的，还是比较快乐的皮诺。
which is what or it will rather
momentarily or does rather hapi-pino.
你可以看到它从快乐和快乐中下载
So you can see here it
downloads from hapi/happy and
下载 hapi-pino ，它是一种用于幸福 js的测井工具。
downloads hapi-pino which is
a logging tool for happiness js.
正如你所看到的，这现在有两个依赖性，所以我们要做的是
So as you can see, this has now two
dependencies, so what we're gonna do is
我们要进入我们的指挥线我要关闭我的侧边栏
we're gonna come into our command line
here, I'm gonna close my sidebar here.
好吧我在哪儿
All right, so, where am I?
我在 nodejs ，所以我要直接
I am in nodejs so
I'm gonna go up a directly and
在更复杂的节点应用中我会说 npm， init-y ，所以
into more complicated node app,
and I'm gonna say npm, init-y, so
如果您的主机上未安装 nodejs ，那么首先
first of all if you don't have nodejs
installed like on your host computer
你可能要去做这件事很容易安装
you probably will have to go do that,
it's pretty easy to install.
我知道所以我要在晚上说
I do, so I'm gonna say npm init- y,
我建议不要在节点 10 或节点 12上使用。
I would suggest being on
neither node 10 or node 12.
我现在就在 10 号节点上，但这很容易就能有 12 个。
I'm on node 10 right now, but
this would work easily just as well as 12.
好的，节点 npm- y 仅为您生成一个 package.json ，并且
Okay, and node npm- y just generates
a package.json for you, and
意思就是不要问我有什么问题
the- y means don't ask me
any questions just do it.
所以现在如果你看这里
So now if you look in here it say,
我在那里有 package.json ，对吧 ?
I have package.json right there, right?
我会说 mpm 安装我会说 @happy/ 快乐
And I'm going to say mpm install,
and I'm gonna say @happy/ happy,
像这样快乐的皮诺
and happy-pino like that.
人们经常问我你不需要 --省省吧，
People frequently ask me like don't you
need --save that's not required anymore,
NodeJS 刚刚自动执行该操作。
NodeJS just just automatically does it.
看其实有一面旗帜不保存就是应该这样
See actually there's a flag to not
save which is how it should have been
第一个地方就这样
in the first place, there we go.
我们安装了 73 个软件包，现在你可以看到我有一个节点模块目录，
We installed 73 packages, And you can see
now that I have a node modules directory,
我有个 package.JSON package.JSON，您也可以完全使用纱线来完成此操作，
I have a package.JSON package.JSON, you
could totally do this with yarn as well,
我对他们的工作都没有意见。
I have no opinion on the matter
they both do the job adequately.
我只是用 MPM 是因为它很棒而且已经安装好了
I just use MPM because it's great and
it's already installed and
我不需要为它做任何事
I don't have to do anything for it.
好吧我现在有个计划如果你想看看
All right, so now I have an entire
project if you wanna just see what if it
如果节点索引为 js ，那么您可以看到它现在正在运行。
works if the node index-js,
you can see there that it's now running.
如果我点击此处的链接种类
If I click here on this link
kind of opens here, and
你可以在这里看到它回来的有点 json 只是一个成功的真假
you can see here that it's returning
a bit of json that's just a success:true.
然后我就会把你的反应
And then I'll put a bunch of information
about what the response was and
所有这些东西的要求
the request, all that kind of stuff.
所以我要把它关掉然后我们就回来
So I'm gonna shut that down and
we're gonna come back over here,
现在我们要在我们的公司内部创建一个 Docker 文件
so now we're gonna create
a Docker file inside of our
更复杂的节点应用程序，比如新的文件， Docker 文件。
more complicated node app and
say new file, Docker file.
我们要从你想象的节点开始
We're gonna start from as you
may imagine node:12-stretch,
你可以做拉伸或拉伸的
and you can do stretch or
stretch-slim, but
在这一点上我们都安装了拉伸装置，所以我在这里的 Docker 扩展。
at this point we all have stretch
installed, so my Docker extension here.
Cuz ，我为 Visual Studio 代码安装了 Docker 扩展，
Cuz I have a Docker extension
installed for Visual Studio Code which
我建议你们全部安装，我们在微软维护它，所以我认为它是可以的。
I suggest all of you install, we maintain
it at Microsoft so I think it's okay.
它也会为你做这些自动完成的工作。
It'll do these kind of auto
completions for you as well.
我的意思是我不会在这个过程中过度过度
And, I mean, I'm not actually gonna go
over it too much in this course, but
你知道的这很值得在这里探索所有这些我们所做的事情
just so you know, it is worth exploring
here, all this stuff that we're doing from
命令行，您可以直接从 VS 代码运行。
the command line, you could
totally run directly from VS code.
好了从那 12 号节点到那里
All right, so from node 12 stretch there,
我要说的是和以前一样的用户节点
I'm gonna say user node
just like we did before,
在那儿工作我们要做 /home/node/ 代码
work there and
we're gonna do /home/node/code.
我们要做的就是要复制
And what we're going to do
is we're gonna say copy,
-- 像我们以前一样， chown 节点冒号节点。
-- chown node colon node
like we did before.
但我要把这个目录里的所有东西都复制到家庭/节点 / 代码中，对吧 ?
But I'm gonna say copy everything in this
directory over into home/node/code, right?
所以就把一切都移到了容器里
So it just moves everything
over into the container, so
这一点就意味着这里的一切都变成了这里的一切
that's what the dot does means everything
from here goes into everything over there.
好的我想说的是 CMD["节点 "
Okay at this point I
want to say CMD["node",
index.js "] 对吗 ?
index.js"] right?
所以这看起来好像是一样的
So this looks relatively the same,
我们从最后一节真正改变的就是这个
the only thing that we really changed
from the last section is this.
所以我要结束我的工作了再次把它称为我的纸条应用
So I'm gonna close that I'm just gonna
continue calling it my note app, again,
如果你想让他们去的话你可以给他们打个电话
you can call these different
things if you want them to,
我不太在意所以我要再把它改写
I don't particularly care, so
I'm gonna just overwrite it again.
所有东西都应该起作用，我应该可以，运行我的应用程序。
And everything should just work, and
I should be able to, Run my app.
这就是工作，这很好，但那是因为我在我的工作上做了 MPM 的安装。
So this is working, and that's fine, but
that's because I did the MPM install on my
电脑是几个问题但有一个
host computer,
it's a couple problems but there's one,
如果您在 CI 中运行此节点，那么节点模块将不存在，对吗 ?
if you're running this in CI then the node
modules won't already be there, right?
因为我们没有落实节点模块，这是第一个问题，
Because we don't commit our node modules,
that's the first problem,
第二个问题是节点有本机模块的概念，是吗 ?
the second problem is node has
the concept of native modules, right?
因此，如果我正在运行类似节点 SAS( 即本机模块 ) 的内容，那么它将写入
So if I'm running something like node SAS,
which is a native module, it's written in
C，它不是用 JavaScript 编写的，它将为 Mac OS 构建。
C, it's not written in JavaScript,
it's going to build that for Mac OS.
然后如果我把它复制到 Ubuntu 或 Debian ，在这个特定的情况下，
And then if I copy that into Ubuntu or
Debian, in this particular case,
它不会起作用，对，因为 Mac OS 与 Debian不一样。
it's not going to work, right, because Mac
OS is very much not the same as Debian.
所以我们要做的就是要在里面运行 MPM
So what we have to do is we have
to run MPM install inside of
集装箱对吧
the container, right?
这必须在容器内发生。
That has to happen
inside of the container.
所以让我们先停一下然后证明我的观点
So let's go ahead and stop this,
and just to prove my point,
如果我现在说除去 node_modules ，
if I say remove node_modules right now,
如果我每次打字都有个镍我就会很有钱
if I had a nickel for every time I
typed this, I'd be a very rich man.
好了如果我再做一次我就跑了
All right, so now if I build it again,
and I do run,
就会是，我不不明白，对吧 ?
it is gonna be like,
I don't not understand this, right?
因为它不会找到任何模块对吧
Because it's not gonna find
any of those modules, right?
所以我们就不能依赖节点模块了，所以
So we can't depend on the node
modules actually being there, so
我们要做的就是我们要来这里说 RUN
what we're gonna do, is we're gonna
come in here and we're gonna to say RUN,
这将运行任何您希望其运行的任意 shell 命令，运行 npm。
this runs any sort of arbitrary shell
command that you want it to run, run npm.
而你们中的大多数人可能想在晚上做安装，对吧 ?
And as most of you would probably
think to run npm install, right?
我想建议一个比晚上做的更好
I'm gonna suggest one that I think
is better than npm install for
这个， npmci ，所以晚上的 ci 其实是要
this, npmci so npm ci is actually going to
包好包包里的东西吧
adhere to whatever is in
the package-lock.json, right?
所以这个实际上是被锁定到非常具体的版本，
So this is actually locked down
to very specific versions,
这就是你喜欢的自动化环境对吧
which is what you want in your like
automation environments, right?
你想让它像所有东西一样接近
You want it to be like exactly
as close to everything as
可能是你的速度更快
possible that you had, and it's faster.
它忽略 MPM 安装对您和
It ignores a bunch of stuff that
MPM Install does for you and
MPMCI 不需要这样做，它的运行速度也很快。
MPMCI doesn't need to do so,
it actually runs fast as well.
因此，在 Docker 文件中，我将邀请您不要使用 MPM 安装，
So inside of Docker files I'm going
to invite you to not use MPM Install,
而是用 MPMCI 来做最好的练习
use MPMCI instead,
Kind of a best practice there.
好了如果我再回来再建
All right, so now if I come
back in here and build again,
这个步骤要长一点，对，
This step will take a bit longer, right,
它会穿过整个国家的国家防范机制发生了什么
cuz it's gonna go through and
all the NPM installs, what happened?
是，这会是个问题，所以现在我们正在进入许可错误。
Yes, this would be a problem, so
now we're running into permission errors.
所以现在的问题是它不拥有代码
So the issue now is that it doesn't
own code, you're gonna run into
当您使用 Docker时，所有时间都将发生许可权错误，
permission errors all the time
when you're working with Docker,
就像是为了这个前提而准备好
like just buckle up and
be prepared for for such a premise.
所以如果我经营 Ls- lsh，我可以在这里看到，这就是
So if I run Ls- lsh,
I could see in here, That this
特定目录由 root 用户拥有，因此当我尝试执行 npm 安装时，
particular directory is owned by root,
so when I'm trying to do npm install,
它正在尝试更改此根目录，这是一个问题，对吗 ?
it's trying to make changes to this
root directory, that's a problem, right?
那么我们是如何处理这个问题的呢 ?
So how do we handle this?
你要处理的就是你要去
Well, the way that you're gonna
handle is you're gonna go instead
在这里做这个工作的人总是会把它作为一个节点或路线。
of doing this worker right here, this is
always gonna do it as node or as route.
我不认为你能告诉它即使是在哪里
I don't think you can tell it
necessarily even where to do it yeah,
我不认为你能
I don't think you can.
所以我们要做的不是说
So, what we're gonna do
instead of instead of saying,
让我们的创意就在这里
letting that creative we're
just gonna say right here,
运行它们的主/节点 / 代码。
run make their home/node/code.
现在，因为这是用户节点，所以它将作为节点用户运行。
Now because this is user node right here,
it is going to run this as the node user.
如果我再这样做现在一切都能做得到
Now, if I do it again,
Now it's gonna be able to do everything
因为它是正确的用户现在如果我们再次运行它
that it needs to because it is the correct
user, and now if we go run this again,
一切都应该做，因为我用出版
Everything should be working it and
because I ran with publish
就在这里 3000 3000我们应该可以在这里打开链接
right here 3000 3000, we should be
able to go in here and open link.
很酷吧
Very cool, right?
好吧我想打电话给你因为这是我碰到的问题
All right, something I do wanna call out
here because it's an issue I ran into when
我在做这个难免有一个你也要这样做
I was making this and inevitably one
of you is going to run this as well.
注意这里而不是我绑定到 0000 的快乐
Notice here instead of
happy I bind to host 0000,
如果我将此绑定到 localhost，那么在 100 个端点中的 99 次
if I bind this to localhost,
which 99 times out of 100 ends
这样在语义上是一样的，这就不起作用了。
up being semantically the same like that,
this will not work.
当您在 localhost 上运行容器时，这将不允许其转义容器。
This will not allow this to escape the
container when you run it on localhost,
它是一个难以逃避的循环，对吧 ?
it's a hard loop back that it
cannot escape itself, right?
所以我们要绑定到 0000 才能让你离开
So, that's why we have to bind to 0000
that will allow you to get outside of
货柜
the container